Guide to the Liederkranz Collection ca. 1847-1987 MSS.130
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Printed Sheet Music Collection
  - Composer: Kipper, Hermann Title: Der Todte Schneider Uniform Title: Todte Schneider Plate Number: M.S. 351., undated (Box 117, Folder 1669)
  - Composer: Kipper, Hermann Title: Der todte Schneider Uniform Title: Todte Schneider Publisher information: Cologne (Germany): M. Schloss, undated (Box 117, Folder 1670)
  - Composer: Kipper, Hermann Title: Die Gerichtssitzung Uniform Title: Gerichtssitzung Plate Number: M.S.225., undated (Box 121, Folder 1737)
  - Composer: Kipper, Hermann Title: Die Gerichtssitzung Uniform Title: Gerichtssitzung Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Ries & Erler Plate Number: R. 5007 E., undated (Box 121, Folder 1736)
  - Composer: Kipper, Hermann Title: Fidelia. Quodlibet Oper in 2 Acten Uniform Title: Fidelia Publisher information: Cologne (Germany): M. Schloss (W. Clouth, Cologne [printer]) Plate Number: M.S.626, undated (Box 125, Folder 1808)
  - Composer: Kipper, Hermann Title: Kellner und Lord Uniform Title: Kellner und Lord Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 4776, undated (Box 123, Folder 1766)
  - Composer: Kirchl, Adolf Title: Das schonste Lied Uniform Title: Schonste Lied Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 8109, undated (Box 147, Folder 2080)
  - Composer: Kirchl, Adolf Title: Elfenlocken im Wald Uniform Title: Elfenlocken im Wald Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bosworth & Co. (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: B. & Co. 7102, undated (Box 154, Folder 2392)
  - Composer: Kirchl, Adolf Title: Elslein mach' auf Uniform Title: Elsein mach' auf Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 4534, undated (Box 157, Folder 2488)
  - Composer: Kirchl, Adolf Title: Es muss ein Wunderbares sein Uniform Title: Es muss ein Wunderbares sein Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Adolf Robitschek Plate Number: A. R. 1356a., undated (Box 157, Folder 2479)
  - Composer: Kirchl, Adolf Title: Es muss ein Wunderbares sein Uniform Title: Es muss ein Wunderbares sein Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): Robay & Robitschek (Jos. Eberle & Co., Vienna [printer]) Plate Number: R. & R. 1356., undated (Box 157, Folder 2478)
  - Composer: Kirchl, Adolf Title: Es war einst eine schone Zeit Uniform Title: Es was einst eine schone Zeit Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 8305-3, undated (Box 160, Folder 2609)
  - Composer: Kirchl, Adolf Title: Frau Wirtin, schenkt ein! Uniform Title: Frau Wirtin, schenkt ein! Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 4657 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 161, Folder 2639)
  - Composer: Kirchl, Adolf Title: Im Abendwinde Uniform Title: Im Abendwinde Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 4306 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 164, Folder 2763)
  - Composer: Kirchl, Adolf Title: Orakel Uniform Title: Orakel Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 4568 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 167, Folder 2895)
  - Composer: Kirchl, Adolf Title: Stillleben Uniform Title: Stillleben Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bosworth & Co. Plate Number: B. & Co. 7099, undated (Box 171, Folder 3051)
  - Composer: Kistler, Cyrill Title: Kunihild. Overture Uniform Title: Kunihild. Overture, Act 3 Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Carl Simon Plate Number: C.S.2049 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 32, Folder 383)
  - Composer: Kistler, Cyrill Title: Kunihild. Overture Uniform Title: Kunihild. Overture, Act 3 Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Carl Simon Plate Number: C.S.2050 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 32, Folder 384)
  - Composer: Kistler, Cyrill Title: Kunihild. Prelude Uniform Title: Kunihild. Overture, Act 3; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 19864-20, undated (Box 32, Folder 385)
  - Composer: Klanert, Karl Title: Von dir zu scheiden Uniform Title: Von dir zu scheiden Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Robert Forberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 6462 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 152, Folder 2288)
  - Composer: Klanert, Karl Title: Vor dir zu scheiden Uniform Title: Vor dir zu scheiden Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Robert Forberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 6462 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 101, Folder 1323)
  - Composer: Klee, Eugen Title: Das Ringlein Sprang Entzwei Uniform Title: Ringlein Sprang Entzwei Publisher information: Philadelphia: J. W. Jost Plate Number: 552, undated (Box 150, Folder 2173)
  - Composer: Klee, Eugen Title: Das stille Thal Uniform Title: Stille Thal Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 21006-3, undated (Box 146, Folder 2073)
  - Composer: Klee, Eugen Title: Fruhlings Erwachen Uniform Title: Fruhlings Erwachen Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 21005-15, undated (Box 157, Folder 2486)
  - Composer: Klee, Eugen Title: Serenade Uniform Title: Serenade Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 14580-2 1/2, undated (Box 170, Folder 3006)
  - Composer: Klee, Eugen Title: Vereins- und Willkomm' Gruss Uniform Title: Vereins- und Willkomm' Gruss, undated (Box 156, Folder 2447)
  - Composer: Kleffel, Arno Title: On Guard Uniform Title: Auf der Wacht; arr. Publisher information: New York: F. A. Rockar Plate Number: F. A. R. 770-2, undated (Box 151, Folder 2250)
  - Composer: Klein, Bruno Oscar Title: Le Secret d'Amour Uniform Title: Secret d'Amour Publisher information: New York: J. Fischer & Bro. Plate Number: J.F. & B. 3687-4, undated (Box 111, Folder 1596)
  - Composer: Klein, Bruno Oscar Title: No Stars in Heaven Uniform Title: Himmel hat keine Sterne Publisher information: Boston: Oliver Ditson Company Plate Number: 4-66-62739-5, undated (Box 156, Folder 2463)
  - Composer: Klein, Bruno Oscar Title: Soldier's March Uniform Title: Soldaten-Marsch Publisher information: New York ( of Amreica): Edward Schuberth & Co. Plate Number: C.F.T.131, undated (Box 104, Folder 1425)
  - Composer: Kleinfelder, R. Title: Hebe mich auf weichen Schwingen Uniform Title: Hebe mich auf weichen Schwingen Publisher information: New York: Edward Schuberth & Co. Plate Number: E.S. & Co. 3095, undated (Box 161, Folder 2650)
  - Composer: Klengel, Paul Title: Abendruh Uniform Title: Abendruh Publisher information: New York Engraver: Otto Lobner, undated (Box 149, Folder 2137)
  - Composer: Klengel, Paul Title: Bohmisches Volkslied Uniform Title: Bohmisches Volkslied Publisher information: New York Engraver: Otto Lobner, undated (Box 150, Folder 2177)
  - Composer: Klengel, Paul Title: Frohliche Armuth Uniform Title: Frohliche Armuth Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 6645-5, undated, undated (Box 160, Folder 2626)
  - Composer: Klengel, Paul Title: Und botet ihr ein Bisthum mir Uniform Title: Und botet ihr ein Bisthum mir Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 5570, undated (Box 173, Folder 3155)
  - Composer: Kling, Henri Title: The two little Bulfinches Uniform Title: Two little Bulfinches; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 11809-8 1/2, undated (Box 31, Folder 371)
  - Composer: Kling, Henri Title: The two little Bulfinches Uniform Title: Two little Bulfinches; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 11811-19, undated (Box 31, Folder 370)
  - Composer: Klinger, Achilles, arr. Title: Du, du liegst mir im Herzen Uniform Title: Du, du liegst mir im Herzen Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Richard Kaun Plate Number: R.K.802, undated (Box 146, Folder 2072)
  - Composer: Klugescheid, R., arr. Title: Paraphrase uber Mendelssohn's Es ist bestimmt Uniform Title: Paraphrase uber Mendelssohn's Es ist bestimmt, undated (Box 87, Folder 1098)
  - Composer: Klughardt, August Title: Auf der Wanderschaft. Suite fur Orchester Uniform Title: Auf der Wanderschaft. Suite fur Orchester Plate Number: 27, undated (Box 31, Folder 372)
  - Composer: Knight, Launce Title: The Minstrel's Delight. Overture Uniform Title: Minstrel's Delight. Overture; arr. Publisher information: Boston: Oliver Ditson Plate Number: 58957-35-O, undated (Box 31, Folder 373)
  - Composer: Kockert, Otto Title: Prima Ballerina. Intermezzo Uniform Title: Prima Ballerina Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Otto Kockert, undated (Box 109, Folder 1552)
  - Composer: Kockert, Otto Title: Valse chromatique Uniform Title: Valse chromatique; arr. Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Otto Kockert, undated (Box 121, Folder 1739)
  - Composer: Kodaly, Zoltan Title: Transylvanian Lament (Szekely Keserves) Uniform Title: Szekely Keserves, undated (Box 224, Folder 5)
  - Composer: Koemmenich, Louis Title: Abschied Uniform Title: Abschied Publisher information: Philadelphia: J. W. Jost Plate Number: 488, undated (Box 149, Folder 2139)
  - Composer: Kohler, O. Title: The Mice and the Trap Uniform Title: Mice and the Trap; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5869-28, undated (Box 78, Folder 1009)
  - Composer: Kohler, Wilhelm Title: Thuringer Land Uniform Title: Thuringer Land Publisher information: Saalfeld (Germany): Wilhelm Kohler Plate Number: 17339, undated (Box 127, Folder 1844)
  - Composer: Kollner, E. Title: Die Rheingauer Glocken Uniform Title: Rheingauer Glocken Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: G. H. 538 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 170, Folder 2980)
  - Composer: Kollner, E. Title: Vaterlandshymne Uniform Title: Vaterlandshymne Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Friedrich Luckhardt (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. L. 278 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 135, Folder 1906)
  - Composer: Kollner, Ed. Title: Das Lied von 1876 Uniform Title: Lied von 1876 Publisher information: New York: Edward Schuberth & Co., undated (Box 90, Folder 1125)
  - Composer: Komzak, Carl Title: Fideles Wien (Joyous Vienna) Uniform Title: Fideles Wien; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5731-21 1/2, undated (Box 122, Folder 1755)
  - Composer: Komzak, Karl Title: Volksliedchen Marchen Uniform Title: Volksliedchen Marchen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): August Cranz Plate Number: C. 27356., undated (Box 96, Folder 1184)
  - Composer: Komzak, Karl Title: Wiener Volksmusik (Viennese Folk-Music). Potpourri Uniform Title: Wiener Volksmusik. Potpourri; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 14699-106, undated (Box 31, Folder 374)
  - Composer: Koschar, Thomas Title: Drei Mannerchore: Was wol d'Liab is?; Der guate Rath; D'Hamkehr Uniform Title: Was wol d'Liab is?; Der guate Rath; D'Hamkehr Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 3125, undated (Box 148, Folder 2122)
  - Composer: Koschat, Thomas Title: Am Worther See. Karntner Walzer Uniform Title: Am Worther See. Karntner Walzer Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F.E.C.L.3185 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 32, Folder 375)
  - Composer: Koschat, Thomas Title: Ein Sonntag auf der Alm Uniform Title: Sonntag auf der Alm Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 3985 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 97, Folder 1221)
  - Composer: Koschat, Thomas Title: Karthner Volkslied Uniform Title: Karthner Volkslied Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (E. Jul. Pickenhahn, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 2611 Engraver: E. Jul. Pickenhahn, Leipzig, undated (Box 152, Folder 2281)
  - Composer: Koschat, Thomas Title: Mei Freud Uniform Title: Mei Freud Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 4706 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 166, Folder 2836)
  - Composer: Kosma, Joseph Title: Autumn Leaves Uniform Title: Autumn Leaves Publisher information: New York ( of Ameica): Ardmore Music Corp., undated (Box 145, Folder 2036)
  - Composer: Kraemer, E. Title: Ein rheinisches Madchen bei rheinischem Wein Uniform Title: Rheinischen Madchen bei rheinischem Wein Publisher information: New York: Orbis Music Publishing Co., undated (Box 160, Folder 2605)
  - Composer: Kraemer, Emil Title: Der Spielmann Uniform Title: Spielmann Publisher information: Bremen (Germany): Schweers & Haake Plate Number: Sch. & H. 1293, undated (Box 173, Folder 3167)
  - Composer: Kramer, A. Walter Title: At Morning Uniform Title: Des Morgens Publisher information: New York: The John Church Company Plate Number: 17414-5, undated (Box 149, Folder 2147)
  - Composer: Kramer, A. Walter Title: Of all the dreams men dream Uniform Title: Of all the dreams men dream Publisher information: Boston: The Boston Music Co. Plate Number: B.M.Co. 4903, undated (Box 168, Folder 2924)
  - Composer: Kramer, Eduard Title: O lasst mich traumen, traumen beim Wein Uniform Title: O lasst mich traumen, traumen beim Wein, undated (Box 168, Folder 2933)
  - Composer: Krehbiel, Henry E. Title: Russian Boat Song Uniform Title: Russian Boat Song; arr. Publisher information: New York: The John Church Company Plate Number: 10078-1-G, undated (Box 155, Folder 2422)
  - Composer: Kreisler, Fritz Title: Schon Rosmarin Uniform Title: Schon Rosmarin; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 18232-23, undated (Box 32, Folder 376)
  - Composer: Kreisler, Fritz Title: The Old Refrain Uniform Title: Old Refrain; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 22251-5, undated (Box 172, Folder 3109)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard, arr. Title: Klage Uniform Title: Klage Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 3247 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 174, Folder 3232)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard, arr. Title: Klage Uniform Title: Klage Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 3500 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 174, Folder 3233)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard, arr. Title: Liebes-Kundigung Uniform Title: Liebes-Kundigung Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 5056 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 149, Folder 2165)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Altniederlandisches Lied Uniform Title: Altniederlandisches Lied Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): Rebay & Robitschek (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: R. & R. 437a. Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 147, Folder 2095)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Alt-Wien. Walzer Uniform Title: Alt-Wien. Walzer Plate Number: A.W., undated (Box 32, Folder 377)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Balkanbilder Uniform Title: Balkanbilder Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F.E.C.L. 4875, undated (Box 74, Folder 966)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Dagobert. Fanfare Uniform Title: Dagobert. Fanfare Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): Gustav Lewy Plate Number: G.L.II.95, undated (Box 146, Folder 2074)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Dangebet Uniform Title: Dankgebet Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 3247 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 87, Folder 1085)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Dankgebet Uniform Title: Dankgebet; arr. Publisher information: Munich (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 9921, undated (Box 152, Folder 2259)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Dankgebet Uniform Title: Dankgebet Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 3520, undated (Box 87, Folder 1086)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Dankgebeten Uniform Title: Dankgebet, undated (Box 87, Folder 1087)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Das Herzklopfen. Polka francaise Uniform Title: Herzklopfen Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): Buchholz & Diebel (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: B. & D. 309 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 101, Folder 1317)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Das Volkslied Uniform Title: Volkslied Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 4485, undated (Box 172, Folder 3120)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Hymne an die Madonna Uniform Title: Hymne an die Madonna Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 4498, undated (Box 163, Folder 2710)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Hymne an die Madonna Uniform Title: Hymne an die Madonna Publisher information: New York: F. A. Rockar Plate Number: F. A. R. 719., undated (Box 163, Folder 2712)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Hymne an die Madonna Uniform Title: Hymne an die Madonna Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): Gustav Lewy (Jos. Eberle & Co., Vienna [printer]) Plate Number: G. L. H. 36., undated (Box 163, Folder 2711)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Im Winter Uniform Title: Im Winter Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): Rebay & Robitschek (Jos. Eberle & Co., Vienna [printer]) Plate Number: R. & R. 884. Engraver: Jos. Eberle & Co., Vienna, undated (Box 162, Folder 2705)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Love Finds a Way Uniform Title: Love Finds a Way Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 5354, undated (Box 151, Folder 2244)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Sechs Altniederlandische Volkslieder Uniform Title: Sechs Altniederlandische Volkslieder Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): Schrottenbach & Co. (Eberle & Schipek [printer]) Plate Number: F. S. 6 Engraver: Eberle & Schipek, undated (Box 175, Folder 3273)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Sechs Altniederlandischer Volkslieder Uniform Title: Sechs Altniederlandischer Volkslieder Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F.E.C.L. 4705, undated (Box 75, Folder 968)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Singe, trinke, kusse! Uniform Title: Singe, trinke, kusse! Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 5058, undated (Box 172, Folder 3116)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Tanzweise Uniform Title: Tanzweise Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 4966 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 149, Folder 2166)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Uber den Wassern Uniform Title: Uber den Wassern Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 5018 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 172, Folder 3137)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Volkslied aus Oberosterreich Uniform Title: Volkslied aus Oberosterreich Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 8962, undated (Box 152, Folder 2290)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Volkslied aus Oberosterreich Uniform Title: Volkslied aus Oberosterreich Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): Rebay & Robitschek (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: R. R. 732. Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 172, Folder 3119)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Wenn der Vogel naschen will Uniform Title: Wenn der Vogel naschen will Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5560-3, undated (Box 154, Folder 2368)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Wenn Zweie sich gut sind Uniform Title: Wenn Zweie sich gut sind Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 4499, undated (Box 152, Folder 2274)
  - Composer: Kremser, Eduard Title: Wenn Zweie sich gut sind Uniform Title: Wenn Zweie sich gut sind Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): Gustav Lewy (Jos. Eberle & Co., Vienna [printer]) Plate Number: G. L. H. 35., undated (Box 152, Folder 2273)
  - Composer: Krenek, Ernst Title: Blues from the opera Jonny spielt auf Uniform Title: Blues aus der Oper Jonny spielt auf, undated (Box 224, Folder 6)
  - Composer: Kretschmer, Edmund Title: Coronation March from the Opera Folkunger Uniform Title: Folkunger. Coronation March; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 1454-19, undated (Box 32, Folder 381)
  - Composer: Kretschmer, Edmund Title: Eriksgang un Kronungsmarsch aus der Oper Die Folkunger Uniform Title: Die Folkunger. Eriksgang und Kronungsmarsch Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 4583 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 32, Folder 380)
  - Composer: Kretschmer, Edmund Title: Eriksgang und Kronungsmarsch aus der Oper Die Folkunger Uniform Title: Die Folkunger. Eriksgang un Kronungsmarsch Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 4273, 4335 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 32, Folder 378)
  - Composer: Kretschmer, Edmund Title: Kronungsmarsch Uniform Title: Die Folkunger. Kronungsmarsch Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 4336 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 32, Folder 379)
  - Composer: Kretschmer, William F. Title: Koschat-March Uniform Title: Koschat. March Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5636-17, undated (Box 109, Folder 1553)
  - Composer: Kreutzer, Conradin Title: Die Kapelle Uniform Title: Kapelle Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 9558, undated (Box 152, Folder 2267)
  - Composer: Kreutzer, Conradin Title: Fruhlingsnahen (Spring's Approach) Uniform Title: Fruhlingsnahen Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Friedrich Luckhardt (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. L. 952 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 153, Folder 2335)
  - Composer: Kreutzer, Conradin Title: Fruhlingsnahen (Spring's Approach) Uniform Title: Fruhlingsnahen Publisher information: New York: Edward Schuberth & Co., undated (Box 153, Folder 2336)
  - Composer: Kreutzer, Conradin Title: Fruhlingsnahen Uniform Title: Fruhlingsnahen Plate Number: 4243.17., undated (Box 160, Folder 2618)
  - Composer: Kreutzer, Conradin Title: Gesange Uniform Title: Mai Gesang Plate Number: 2160.5, undated (Box 158, Folder 2525)
  - Composer: Kreutzer, Conradin Title: Schafers Sonntagslied Uniform Title: Schafers Sonntagslied Plate Number: 4651, undated (Box 170, Folder 3014)
  - Composer: Kreutzer, Conradin Title: Schafer's Sonntagslied Uniform Title: Schafers Sonntagslied Publisher information: New York: Edward Schuberth & Co., undated (Box 170, Folder 3016)
  - Composer: Kreutzer, Conradin Title: Schafer's Sonntagslied Uniform Title: Schafers Sonntagslied Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): Theodor Rattig (Jos. Eberle & Co., Vienna [printer]) Plate Number: T. R. 193, undated (Box 170, Folder 3015)
  - Composer: Kreutzer, Rodolphe Title: Etudes Uniform Title: Etudes ou caprices, violin Plate Number: 6429, undated (Box 103, Folder 1395)
  - Composer: Kriens, Christiaan Title: In Holland. Suite for Small Orchestra. Wooden Shoe Dance Uniform Title: In Holland. Wooden Shoe Dance Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 13692-30, undated (Box 32, Folder 382)